androidphonesoft.com 2015-06-08

# Androidphonesoft Privacy Policy

## Privacy

At Androidphonesoft, your security and privacy is the utmost importance to us. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to Androidphonesoft's commitment to protect your privacy. Androidphonesoft will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

As such, Androidphonesoft is committed to ensuring that its customers are informed as to how their personal information will be used and kept secure. 

**  
1\. What information do we collect? What do we use it for?**  
When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

**2\. How do 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?**  
Androidphonesoft uses secure server hosted by Regnow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

**3\. About cookies**  
In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies can also determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

**4\. Our companywide commitment to your privacy**  
This policy covers the our website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Androidphonesoft employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.
